const myApp = [{
    question: "javaScript started with?",
    options: ["<plaintext><scritp>...<scritp>", "<plaintext><Javascript>...<javascript>", "<plaintext><java> </java>", "all above"],
    answer: 0,
    description: " <plaintext><Scritp> ... <scritp> That's the correct answer.",
}, {
    question: "Web pages are written in?",
    options: ["FTP", "HTML", "HTTP", "URL"],
    answer: 1,
    description: "Web pages are written in HTML.",
}, {
    question: "You can get the value of an element's attributes using ...... method.",
    options: ["setAttribute method", "getElementById method", "getAttribute method", "All of above"],
    answer: 2,
    description: "You can get the value of an element's attributes using getAttribute method",
}, {
    question: "What property holds the text content, as well as all nested HTML content, of an element?",
    options: ["innerContent", "innerHTML", "innerWidth", "innerHeight"],
    answer: 1,
    description: "The answer is innerHTML.",
}, {
    question: "The document.getElementById method grabs an element from the DOM using its ......?",
    options: ["Class name", "Attribute", "Id", "Object"],
    answer: 2,
    description: "The answer is Id.",
}, {
    question: "You can set the value of an element's attributes using ...... method?",
    options: ["setAttribute method", "getElementById method", "getAttribute method", "All of above"],
    answer: 0,
    description: "You can set the value of an element's attributes using setAttribute method",
}, {
    question: "You can use the window object's ....... property to set an event handler, or callback, function for the load event.",
    options: ["onload", "load", "addEventListener", "querySelector"],
    answer: 0,
    description: "The onload property allows us to set an event handler or callback function for the load event.",
}, {
    question: "A ........ is a function expression that has no name.",
    options: ["anonymous function", "function declaration", "function name", "function reference"],
    answer: 0,
    description: "Anonymous function is a function expression that has no name.",
}, {
    question: "...... are functions defined inside another function.",
    options: ["Internal functions", "Multiple functions", "Function home", "Nested functions"],
    answer: 3,
    description: "Nested functions are functions defined inside antoehr function.",
}, {
    question: "The ...... object is always at the top of the DOM tree.",
    options: ["head", "body", "HTML", "document"],
    answer: 3,
    description: "Document is always at the tope of the DOM tree.",
}];